Here's one way to define a linear learner.
下面说说我是如何定义 LinearLearner 的
I've inputted the linear learner estimator from SageMaker,
我从 SageMaker 导入了 LinearLearner estimator
then the first thing I'm doing is specifying where in
首先指定要将保存的模型属性
our s3 bucket I want to place the saved model attributes.
存储到 S3 存储桶的哪个位置
In this case, specifying a prefix credit card and
指定 prefix“creditcard”
then a full output path in s3 which
然后指定 S3 中的完整路径
points to the bucket and to this directory credit card.
它会指向这个存储桶以及这个目录“creditcard”
This is just good practice to get into because it helps organize the contents of
指定输出路径是一种很好的习惯
your s3 bucket and means you can always
因为这样有助于整理 S3 存储桶中的内容
access a saved model from a known location leader.
并且以后始终可以从已知位置访问保存的模型
Then I'm instantiating an estimator called
然后实例化一个 estimator 叫做 linear
linear and passing in arguments to linear learner.
向 LinearLearner 传入参数
You can see my usual SageMaker parameters and passing in the role,
这些是常规的 SageMaker 参数 包括角色
the SageMaker session, and the output path that I just defined,
SageMaker 会话以及刚刚定义的输出路径
and also specifying details about the train instance.
还设定了训练实例
I want one instance that the c4 xlarge.
实例数量为 1 个 类型为 c4 xlarge
Then for this linear learner,
对于这个 LinearLearner
I need to specify the predictor type.
我需要指定预测器类型
This tells my estimator that I want it to be
它可以告诉 estimator
a binary classifier rather than a regression algorithm.
我需要二元分类器 而不是回归算法
Finally, I'm passing in a number of epochs to train for.
最后传入训练周期数
It turns out that the default value number of epochs is 15 and this is just the number
周期数的默认值为 15
of times that our algorithm will iterate over our entire training set as it learns.
表示算法遍历整个训练集的次数
My idea here is that I'll start with the default
我的策略是先从默认值开始
and then if it looks like I could use more training,
如果还需要训练的话
I'll up the number of epochs but if it looks like my loss decreases really quickly,
我就增大周期数 如果损失下降很快
I can consider decreasing this number.
则减小这个数字
Now that we've instantiated an estimator,
实例化 estimator 后
I want to actually train it on our training data.
下面使用训练数据训练 estimator
As for any built-in algorithm,
与任何内置算法一样
you'll need to format the training data but the split function returned,
需要格式化 split 函数返回的训练数据
first into a non-pie float data array and then into a record set format.
首先转换成 NumPy 浮点数组 然后转换成 RecordSet 格式
So your next task will be to format this data and train the estimator.
下个任务是格式化此数据并训练 estimator
If you make it past this point,
完成此任务后
you'll be given some instructions to deploy the trainer model.
请继续阅读如何部署已训练模型的说明
If you want to check your work,
如果你想检查你的代码
I'll quickly go over a solution in the next video.
请观看下个解答视频